schmap.it 2011-12-31

# Schmaps & Schnaps - privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

We recognize and respect your desire for privacy: please read the following provisions to learn more about our privacy policy.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information refers to information that is personally identifiable such as name, date of birth, address, or phone number. We do not require any personal information from our users: we currently have no registration process, while our user login process verifies user accounts with Twitter. If you enter personal information into schmaps that you make with this service, then such information will be publicly viewable.

### FINANCIAL INFORMATION

We do not require end users to provide any financial information (credit card numbers, etc.). If anyone contacts you by email or otherwise claiming to represent Schmap and asks for your personal or financial information, please be aware that this is a fraudulent representation. You may report any such fraudulent activity to the Internet Fraud Complaint Center at [http://www.ic3.gov](http://www.ic3.gov/).

### COOKIES

In common with many websites, we use cookies (small data files that we transfer to your hard disk) to collect additional website usage data and to improve our service. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions: you can also instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit.

### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

This website contains links to third party web sites. We do not control how these third party web sites collect and use information about their users and therefore we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such third party sites.

### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

We may update this policy from time to time: please check this page for such updates.

### TERMS OF USE

For more information on the terms and conditions that apply to the use of Schmap's web site, please review our Terms of Use.

Effective: October 12th, 2009
